

Game Producer / Project Manager





acjh13@gmail.com



Highly adaptive and multi-disciplinary Producer / Project Manager. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

Experience

Production Intern | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - *Final Fantasy Brave Exvius* Sept 2020 – Present

- Prepared and maintained monthly and weekly event lists for content updates with <u>Google Sheets</u> and <u>Confluence</u>
- Created and followed-up on Design team tasks with <u>Jira</u> after <u>Daily Scrum</u>
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Took initiative to create script to streamline production workflow

Production Teaching Assistant | DigiPen Singapore Sept 2019 – Mar 2020

Advised student game teams on project scoping and task scheduling

- Mediated cross-discipline discussions and conflicts
- Assisted teams with project scope and scheduling issues

Projects

Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer

Kindred | Sept 2019 - June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D single player narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Worked closely with team members of 4 disciplines
- Communicated game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted <u>Agile</u> methodology with weekly <u>Scrum</u> meetings and <u>Kanban</u> task boards
- Created <u>cross-department workflows</u> for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Worked closely with team members of 4 disciplines
- Led and organized weekly meetings with team members
- Worked with lecturers and team members to overcome internal conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!

Education

BSc Computer Science and Game Design

DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore Sept 2017 – May 2021 (Expected)

Dean's Honour List, Fall 2019

Skills

Soft Skills

- Effective Communication
- Problem Solving
- Organisation

Management Methods

- Agile
- Scrum
- Kanban

Management Software

- Jira
- Confluence
- Trello
- Microsoft Excel
- Google Sheets
- HacknPlan

Software & Tools

- Git / SVN
- Microsoft Office
- Visual Studio
- Unity
- Unreal Engine 4
- Custom Game Engine(s)

Programming & Scripting

- C/C++
- C#
- Python
- JavaScript